(
"ai_sub_version": "1.10.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-pro-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"encoder": "h264_qsv"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
Thank you all for joining us today for Baelz Hakos' Birthday Live 2026.
Before we begin, I have a few requests and reminders for everyone.
Feel free to enjoy food and drinks
in front of your TV, PC, or smartphone,
but please be careful not to spill anything on your keyboard.
The official hashtag for this stream is #ReCOLOR3D.
Please post about us on social media.
Taking photos with your camera or smartphone
during the show is more than welcome.
We'd love it if you could share them online
to help spread the excitement.
The show will begin shortly, so please stay tuned.
皆様、本日はハコス・ベールズ生誕祭2026にお越しくださいまして、
Thank you all for joining us today for Hakos Baelz's Birthday Live 2026.
誠にありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
開演に先立ちまして、皆様にお願いとご案内を申し上げます。
Before we begin, I have a few requests and announcements for everyone.
テレビやパソコン、スマートフォンの前では飲食は可能ですが、
Feel free to enjoy food and drinks in front of your TV, PC, or smartphone,
キーボードに零さないようにお気をつけください。
but please be careful not to spill anything on your keyboard.
当配信のハッシュタグは #ReCOLOR3D です。
The hashtag for this stream is #ReCOLOR3D.
SNSでたくさんポストしてください。
Please post about us on social media.
開演中、カメラやスマートフォンなどによる写真撮影は大歓迎です。
Taking photos with your camera or smartphone during the show is more than welcome.
たくさんポストして盛り上がってくださいますと幸いです。
We'd love it if you could share them and help spread the excitement.
それでは開演までしばらくお待ちください。
The show will begin shortly, so please stay tuned.
Thank you all for joining us today for Baelz Hakos' Birthday Live 2026.
Before we begin, I have a few requests and reminders for everyone.
Feel free to enjoy food and drinks
in front of your TV, PC, or smartphone,
but please be careful not to spill anything on your keyboard.
The official hashtag for this stream is #ReCOLOR3D.
Please post about us on social media.
Taking photos with your camera or smartphone
during the show is more than welcome.
We'd love it if you could share them online
to help spread the excitement.
The show will begin shortly, so please stay tuned.
皆様、本日はハコス・ベールズ生誕祭2026にお越しくださいまして、
Thank you all for joining us today for Hakos Baelz's Birthday Live 2026.
誠にありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
開演に先立ちまして、皆様にお願いとご案内を申し上げます。
Before we begin, I have a few requests and announcements for everyone.
テレビやパソコン、スマートフォンの前では飲食は可能ですが、
Feel free to enjoy food and drinks in front of your TV, PC, or smartphone,
キーボードに零さないようにお気をつけください。
but please be careful not to spill anything on your keyboard.
当配信のハッシュタグは #ReCOLOR3D です。
The hashtag for this stream is #ReCOLOR3D.
SNSでたくさんポストしてください。
Please post about us on social media.
開演中、カメラやスマートフォンなどによる写真撮影は大歓迎です。
Taking photos with your camera or smartphone during the show is more than welcome.
たくさんポストして盛り上がってくださいますと幸いです。
We'd love it if you could share them and help spread the excitement.
それでは開演までしばらくお待ちください。
The show will begin shortly, so please stay tuned.
光の速さで駆け抜ける衝動は
The impulse running through at the speed of light,
何を犠牲にしても
No matter what I sacrifice,
叶えたい強さの覚悟
Is the resolve for the strength I want to grant.
(Don't fear) 一度きりの (One chance)
(Don't fear) Only once (One chance)
(Trust you) この瞬間に賭けてみろ
(Trust you) Bet on this moment,
自分を信じて
Believe in yourself.
時には運だって必要と言うのなら
If they say luck is necessary sometimes,
宿命の旋律も引き寄せてみせよう
I'll show you I can draw in even the melody of fate.
走れ 今を まだ終われない
Run through the now, it can't end yet,
辿り着きたい場所があるから
Because there's a place I want to reach,
その先へと進め
Advance beyond that.
涙さえも強く胸に抱きしめ
Embracing even the tears strongly in my heart,
そこから始まる Story
The story starting from there,
果てしなく続く Winning the soul
Endlessly continuing, Winning the soul.
掴め 今を 変えたいなら
Seize the now, if you want to change,
描いて夢を
Paint your dreams,
未来に掲げ恐れないで挑め
Hoist them to the future, challenge without fear.
走れ 今を まだ終われない
Run through the now, it can't end yet,
辿り着きたい場所があるから
Because there's a place I want to reach,
その先へと進め
Advance beyond that.
涙さえも強く胸に抱きしめ
Embracing even the tears strongly in my heart,
そこから始まる Story
The story starting from there,
果てしなく続く Winning the soul
Endlessly continuing, Winning the soul.
Versus!
Whoa oh whoa oh...
What's up everyone!
I am Chaos, the end of ends,
I still race trapped in the cage of ice,
Your best friend Baelz Hakos from Hololive English Promise!
我はカオス、終わりの果て、ザ・エンド
I am Chaos, the End of Ends, The End.
氷の檻に粉砕し、黒鉄の薔薇
Shattering in the cage of ice, the iron rose.
汝の友、ホロライブのハコス・ベールズです！
Thy friend, Hololive's Hakos Baelz!
Witness me!!
Ah, another year!
Another... not birthday live!
Thank you so much for coming everyone!
Did you like the opening act?
The opening show? Dun dun!
Thank you so much for coming everyone.
This year, we have a not-birthday birthday live again called...
ReCOLOR 3D!
That is also the hashtag, please use it. ReCOLOR 3D.
Um, I dunno, it might be... the theme this year was "Color".
For... for many reasons.
There's also a lot of special things that are happening today.
Uh, as you may or may not already know,
There's a lot of NEW things being revealed in this live.
Maybe a new song?
Maybe a new outfit?
I dunno! You're just gonna have to wait and see.
えーと、今年も誕生日じゃない誕生日ライブやりたいと思います
Um, this year too, I'd like to do a not-birthday birthday live.
みんな来てくれてありがとうございます！
Thank you everyone for coming!
ええ、今日のライブでね、新しいものいっぱいあると思いますので
Yeah, I think there are lots of new things in today's live,
最後まで見てくれたら嬉しいです！
So I'd be happy if you watched until the end!
あ、もう疲れてる、やばい。
Ah, I'm already tired, oh no.
はい！あの、ハッシュタグもぜひぜひ
Yes! Um, please use the hashtag too,
いっぱいコメントと写真をポストしてください
Please post lots of comments and photos.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
Eeto... um, it is my birthday...
Not birthday!
But I'm just so excited to be able to share this day with all of you.
Once I catch my breath, we're gonna get this party started! Yeah?
じゃあ、最後まで楽しみにしてください！
Well then, please look forward to it until the end!
そこ…次の曲ね、ちょっと…
There... the next song, a little...
I'm gonna go to the other stage for the next song,
So I'll see you guys there, alright?
I'm gonna... I'm gonna go now.
Is that alright? Okay, bye! I'll see you guys there.
Race you!
あれが世界なんて
That is the world?
誰の成れの果て
The tragic end of whom?
勝手な悶々
Selfish agony.
答えも欲しいのも奢って
Presuming to want an answer too.
これだけ
Just this.
悩んだって
Even if I worry,
しょうがないじゃんね
It can't be helped, right?
あれは夢だたって
Even if that was a dream,
思うことにしたって
even if I decided to think so,
でも全部重いんだけど
everything feels heavy though.
助けてよ follower
Help me, follower.
抗うだけ
Just resisting,
若さに任せ
leaving it to youth.
Next door, next door
Lucky, lucky, lucky
あるよ
There is,
割り切れたらさ
if I could just divide it distinctly.
降りよう
Let's get off,
楽なのにとか
saying things like 'it's easier'.
Ah, ah
もう嫌だ
I'm sick of it already.
Ah, ah
なんちゅう新世界か
What a new world this is!
あなた以外は
Except for you,
except for you,
Lie, lie, lie, lie
張れないだよ barrier
I can't put up a barrier.
あるはずの何か
Something that should be there,
あったならば
if it existed...
Happy jumping yeah
あんたのその手と
That hand of yours and
あしのこの手を
this hand of mine,
繋いだら
if we connect them,
もう二度と離さないわ
I won't let go ever again.
あんたのその手が
That hand of yours,
あしのこの手を
this hand of mine...
掴んだ
It grasped it.
迷路を
The maze...
見知らぬよ
I don't recognize it.
My love
これで終わりなんて
That this is the end,
贖えないままなんて
that I remain unable to atone...
どうにかなっちゃえて
Wishing it would somehow work out,
願って願ってね
I wish and wish, you know?
遊び去りし
Leaving play behind,
I wonder
Na, mo come on
Checkin' pay, pay
Time to be every day, ma
You did it kera kera
You did it, *cackle cackle*,
Nanbuda-be nan tsunande
Whatever number it is, pinching it.
関係ないな
It doesn't matter.
誰よりも猫
More of a cat than anyone.
演奏ないも結構
No performance is fine too.
足は足だ
Feet are feet.
見といてよ lady
Watch me, lady.
目標で終わらせたいなんて
Wanting to end it as just a goal...
Restart できたらって
Saying 'If I could restart'...
Whoa
でも無理よ
But it's impossible.
もう
Jeez...
What's on your mind?
あるよ
There is,
割り切れたらさ
if I could just divide it distinctly.
降りよう
Let's get off,
楽なのにとか
saying things like 'it's easier'.
Ah, ah
もう嫌だ
I'm sick of it already.
Ah, ah
Ah
なんちゅう新世界か
What a new world this is!
あなた以外は
Except for you,
except for you,
Lie, lie, lie, lie
張れないだよ barrier
I can't put up a barrier.
あるはずの何か
Something that should be there,
あったならば
if it existed...
Happy jumping yeah
あんたのその手と
That hand of yours and
あしのこの手を
this hand of mine,
繋いだら
if we connect them,
もう二度と離さないわ
I won't let go ever again.
あんたのその手が
That hand of yours,
あしのこの手を
this hand of mine...
掴んだ
It grasped it.
迷路を
The maze...
見知らぬよ
I don't recognize it.
My love
Na na na
Whoa
Oh
見知らぬよ My love
I don't recognize it, my love.
La li la li la ta, la li la
Break away, break away, cyber level
アドリブ
Ad-lib.
本気受け止めてる
Taking it seriously.
姿仕草滑稽でしょ
My appearance and gestures are comical, right?
Don't you think?
I'm so lazy
多分数
probably numbers...
Fine, just 並べてる
Fine, just lining up
だけの人
only those people.
Crash, crash
助けて
save me.
Don't you think?
In this world
この頭には
inside this head...
What a beautiful mind
散る花びら
Scattering petals.
Valhalla 行きか
Bound for Valhalla?
飲み体だ
It's a drinking body.
La li la li la ta, la li la
Hey!
誰もが liar
Everyone is a liar.
Hey!
C-R-A-Z-Y, why?
一瞬の感情に
On a momentary emotion,
Ride on, ride on, ride on, ride on
Hey!
心はないわ
There is no heart.
Hey!
狂気の Samurai
The mad Samurai.
Hey!
血走る定めで
With a bloodshot destiny,
引くくらい Ready to die
Ready to die enough to repel.
過渡期は上り
The transition period is rising.
あなたの空 真っ暗な空
Your sky, a pitch-black sky.
あらあら 四苦八苦千切って
Oh my, tearing up the agony.
ほら その場所で
Look, in that place,
聞こえてくる 孤独の仕掛け
you can hear the mechanism of solitude.
轟くのは 己の調べ
What roars is my own melody.
誰かのじゃない 己の調べ
Not someone else's, but my own melody.
Ra-ta-ta, ra-ta-ta-ta
目の前に広がる世界は blue
The world spreading before my eyes is blue.
ひとまず some move
For now, some move.
Pick back, pick tap
There's no need
何その張り切って偉そうに
Why so eager and self-important?
君も愛を
You too, love...
右も左も
Right and left,
知りもしないで 言わないで
don't say it without knowing.
Don't you think?
ニヤリ影が笑う
The grinning shadow laughs.
Hey!
世界は liar
The world is a liar.
Hey!
C-R-A-Z-Y, why?
繰り返すように
As if repeating,
Ride on, ride on, ride on, ride on
偉大な期待の時代の Boy
A boy of the era of great expectations.
Clap back
Losing my mind shooting my side
Fade it あなたのその瞬間
Fade it, that moment of yours.
Maybe nothing wrong nothing wrong
Ladi dadi da ta ladi da
Hey! どれも誇大だ
Hey! It's all exaggerated.
Hey! C R A Z Y
Hey! 一瞬の感情に
Hey! In a fleeting emotion,
Ride on ride on ride on ride on
Hey! 心は '95
Hey! My heart is '95.
Hey! 陽気なサムライ
Hey! A cheerful samurai.
血走らせ多目で
With plenty of bloodshot eyes,
低空 Flight ready to die
Low altitude flight, ready to die.
Hello 日は昇り
Hello, the sun rises.
あなたの空 真っ赤な空
Your sky, a bright red sky.
あらあら 地軸引き千切って
Oh my, tearing the earth's axis apart.
ほらその場所で
Look, right there in that place,
聞こえてくる木霊仕掛け
you can hear the echo mechanism.
驚くのはまだこれから
The surprise is yet to come.
まだこれから
Still yet to come.
あー 待ち侘びて
Ah, waiting impatiently.
時計の針 0時の街
The clock's hands, the city at midnight.
丈だけ低く居座
Sitting low, just the height.
Raise your voice
ほらすぐそこで
Look, right over there,
始まり出す午後の宴
the afternoon banquet begins.
奏でる生 濡れの調べ
Playing life, a wet melody.
唯一無二の 誰の調べ
One of a kind, whose melody?
Peer pressure 注意
Beware of peer pressure.
あいつの信者は多い
That guy has many believers.
己を知りなさい Bitch
Know yourself, bitch.
Hater チラ見やるのに
Even though the haters are glancing.
私もあの人みたいになりたい
I want to be like that person too.
教えて 教えて 幸せですよね
Tell me, tell me, you're happy, right?
もしこのまま消えたら
If I disappear just like this,
愛されるのなら
if I would be loved,
今すぐにでも綺麗に
then even right now, beautifully.
こんなはずないわよ Da Vinci
It shouldn't be like this, Da Vinci.
もう少しだけ待ってね
Just wait a little longer, okay?
コントラストも入れて頂戴
Give me some contrast too.
全世界を懲らしめたい
I want to punish the whole world.
Look at this
Ah, look at this
Look at this 悲しいかも
Look at this, it might be sad.
もう少し肌に艶を頂戴
Give my skin a little more gloss.
女盛り 舐めんなよ Yeah
Don't underestimate a woman in her prime, yeah.
トイレに女神は居ったんかい
Was there a goddess in the restroom?
居ったなら捕まえなさい
If she was there, catch her.
じゃあ見なさい 金マジ可愛い
Then watch, this gold is seriously cute.
私を忘れるな あの嵐
Don't forget me, that storm.
あの時 私はまだ seventeen
At that time, I was still seventeen.
あの時 言ったよな
You said it back then, didn't you?
You can't be beautiful.
You can't be famous.
醜いブスが歌ってんじゃないよ
An ugly hag shouldn't be singing.
あの時狂った精神に
In the mind that went mad back then,
才能が開花
talent bloomed.
味わったコンプ不幸も一般じゃなかった
The complex and misery I tasted weren't ordinary.
本物 君は知ってるかい
Do you know the real thing?
知識と経験の Eros
The eros of knowledge and experience.
まだ使いモンになってるかい
Is it still useful?
女は皆 正気じゃない
Women are all insane.
I'm a beautiful...
Oh look at this
Ah look at this
Look at this
Look at this 悲しいかも
Look at this, it might be sad.
もう少し肌に艶を頂戴
Give my skin a little more gloss.
女盛り 舐めんなよ Yeah
Don't underestimate a woman in her prime, yeah.
トイレに女神は居ったんかい
Was there a goddess in the restroom?
居ったなら捕まえなさい
If she was there, catch her.
Can you hear me, mina, are you beauty?
Can you hear me, everyone, are you beauty?
Say truly, you are the motherfucking beauty
よそ違い 働きなさい
You're mistaken, get to work.
磨いたダイヤ 美しい
A polished diamond, beautiful.
比較的 いや美学的
Comparatively, no, aesthetically.
磨いたダイヤ 美しい
A polished diamond, beautiful.
行きなさい 今見せなさい
Go, show them now.
あなたこそダイヤ 美しい
You are the diamond, beautiful.
I'm a fucking woman and I'm fucking beautiful
God, here I am
We're fucking women and we're fucking beautiful
Yeah!
Ah... Look everyone! I finally have a new outfit!
見て見て見て 新衣装！
Look, look, look! New outfit!
どう？可愛い？どう？どう？
How is it? Cute? How is it? How is it?
Do I look cute?
Ah... is performance Bae?
Ah... is this performance Bae?
Oh! You want to have a close up?
There's so many things I want to show off.
Let's start from the top down. From the head.
Look at that hair! Look at that fade!
かっこよくない？
Isn't it cool?
I asked for a wolf cut.
Um, that's also up half down, so it's really easy to dance in.
めっちゃくちゃ踊りやすくて
It's super easy to dance in.
可愛いでしょ？まあ、可愛い、かっこいいでしょ？
Cute, right? Well, cute, cool... cool, right?
What else? What else?
Oh, my makeup?
メイクも可愛いでしょ？えへへへ。
The makeup is cute too, right? Hehehe.
And then I have so many like, hand accessories as well.
Look at that!
Look how cool that is!
And then we do like a quick scan of the... T-pose quick scan.
Quick scan of the body.
Woah! Woah! Woah!
There's also something very special.
I have an MC tail now.
If you noticed, um, earlier normally when I dance I have my tail just you know free but...
...you know this is the MC resting tail...
...cause the tail also needs resting periods as well.
So this is my MC tail. Very cute.
I hope you guys like it!
Oh my god. And this was designed by...
...of course the amazing Mika Mama!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
めちゃくちゃ可愛いデザインになりました。
It turned into a super cute design.
ありがとうございます。えへへ。
Thank you very much. Hehe.
But that's not all.
I mean, if I get a new outfit, I feel like it's only fair that...
...some other people get new outfits!
来い来い！来て来て来て！
Come, come! Come over here!
Ah! The Bae Dancers also get new outfits!
You get an outfit! You get an outfit! Everyone gets an outfit!
Look at them. Oh, oh look, oh sheesh, oh yeah.
Oh wow. Oh so sexy. Oh.
So the new dancers have also upgraded outfits.
They have shorts with the boots and the socks and the jacket.
Wow, look at that. Amazing.
And then on the back of the jacket, they have my logo.
後ろにロゴもあります。
There's also a logo on the back.
わあ！可愛い！
Wow! Cute!
I also uh designed uh well not designed but I wanted the design to be easy for them to dance in as well so...
This is the upgraded Bae Dance Team! Yay!
どう？可愛い？あん... ポーズ。
How is it? Cute? Um... Pose.
ポーズ。
Pose.
可愛い！イェーイ！
Cute! Yay!
はあ... まあ、せっかくなんでね。
Haa... Well, since it's a special occasion.
Since we all have new outfits, I think it's only fitting that we continue the rest of the live like this...
...with our new outfits!
Ah. じゃあ...
Ah. Then...
踊りますか？
Shall we dance?
We're gonna do the next song uh...
...on that stage over there.
行こう！
Let's go!
はい。はい。おいしょ、おいしょ、おいしょ、おいしょ、おいしょ、おいしょ。
Yes. Yes. Heave-ho, heave-ho, heave-ho, heave-ho, heave-ho, heave-ho.
おいしょ、おいしょ。いや、緊張すんな。
Heave-ho, heave-ho. Man, I'm nervous.
はい！じゃあ、どうぞ！
Okay! Then, go ahead!
正体現せ
Reveal your true form
月の光を飲むわ
I drink the moonlight
僕の夜が来た
My night has come
獣から笑われる One Two
Laughed at by the beasts, One Two
危険を探して Knock Knock Knock
Searching for danger, Knock Knock Knock
Don't mess it up / You gotta make a finger
窓を見て行ける Through my eyes
Look through the window, go through my eyes
その瞳に出会ったら
If I meet those eyes
Oh my / 動かなくなる Come come say it
Oh my / Unable to move / Come come say it
化粧のものか / 魔性のものか
Is it a makeup thing? Is it a demonic thing?
正体現せ / I doubt doubt doubt doubt
Reveal your true form / I doubt doubt doubt doubt
そして Love / 僕見て Know it
And then Love / Look at me, Know it
Lie Lie Lie Lie Yeah
明かせ Love / 存在のうえ
Reveal Love / Above existence
Nai Nai Nai Nai Bye
Shot Shot Shot
Don't worry / 傷つけないよ
Don't worry / I won't hurt you
Lie Lie Lie
I'll let you gonna miss the lady
Ah ah ah ah / See this finger trap?
明日は Make a rough / 今日は Make a fight
Tomorrow Make a rough / Today Make a fight
目を割かないで Make a loud your voice
Don't tear your eyes away Make a loud your voice
よしよし良さそうで
Good good looking good
お狐様に任せよう
Leave it to the Fox God
光を騙して作るんだ Lie
Deceive the light and create a Lie
あちこち目覚めて闇が喝采
Awakening here and there, darkness applauds
ほらこっちおいで
Hey, come over here
Yeah just shut up spell
化粧のものか / 魔性のものか
Is it a makeup thing? Is it a demonic thing?
正体現せ / A da da da da da
Reveal your true form / A da da da da da
未体験 Love / 僕を見て Know it
Unexperienced Love / Look at me, Know it
Lie Lie La La La La Yeah
この世界 / 変えるシミ
This world / The stain that changes it
大体期待して
Mostly expecting it
Shot Shot
Don't worry / 傷つけないよ
Don't worry / I won't hurt you
Lie Lie Yeah
I'll let you search me majority
Ah ah ah ah ah
Hey / Follow the Queen Fox
I'm the ruler of this night
Hey / Follow your Queen Fox
魅せられた
Bewitched
重なり合った
Overlapped
僕達の Show Window
Our Show Window
密か通うこの眼差し
This secret gaze passing back and forth
君に届いた
Reached you
Why don't you know / It's time now
どんな姿でも構わない世界へ
To a world where any form doesn't matter
Yeah
化粧のものか
Is it a makeup thing?
魔性のものか
Is it a demonic thing?
正体現せ
Reveal your true form
Hey そして Love を含みての
Hey, and including Love,
Lai lai la lai ya
明かせた Love 存在の
Revealing the existence of Love,
Nai nai na nai ya
Don't worry 傷つけないよ
Don't worry, I won't hurt you,
Rai yai ya
I'll let you この mystery
I'll let you into this mystery,
Ai yai ya
I'll let you search me, mojani?
Six finger trap!
Ah...
威風堂々
Pomp and Circumstance.
時には噛んだりして
Sometimes biting,
痛みを覚えさせて
Make me remember the pain,
溢れる液体で
With overflowing liquid,
汚してよ全部
Dirty it all up.
足の先からずっと
From the tips of my toes, all the way,
這わせたその神経はもう
Those nerves that crawled...
感触に溺れる
Are drowning in the sensation,
身体 ココロを連れて
Taking body and soul along.
指くわえた我慢の中
Biting my finger in endurance,
欲して逃れそう
Wanting it, I might go crazy.
いらない 全てはいらない
I don't need it, I don't need anything.
磨き上げてる邪魔な PRIDE
That polished, hindering pride,
無意味な世界のルール
The meaningless rules of the world,
くらい無駄としか言いようがない
Can only be called a dark waste.
隠しているあなたの STYLE
Your style that you are hiding,
剥き出しにあるがまま DIVE
Dive in, bare and as you are.
そこに生まれるのは期待
What is born there is expectation,
外れなんかじゃない
It's not a disappointment.
頂きの SMILE
A smile from the peak.
Ah...
吐息を合わせた相性
Compatibility matching our breaths,
耳に吹きかける感情
Emotions breathed into the ear,
破裂しそうな胸
My chest feels like it will burst,
騒ぎ出す細胞
My cells start to riot.
脱ぎかけてる SHIRT
Shirt half taken off,
優しく裂いてよ MAZ
Gently tear it, Maz,
構わず
Don't mind it,
Get flying, my high
躊躇わないで
Don't hesitate,
Darlin'
自由な世界のど真ん中
Right in the middle of a free world.
夢見てんのが本性
Dreaming is my true nature.
いらない 全てはいらない
I don't need it, I don't need anything.
怖気づいた野暮な TRIBE
The boorish tribe that got scared,
満足なんてそこにない
Satisfaction isn't there.
目に見える哀れな未来
The pitiful future visible to the eye,
思い通りにできる LIFE
A life you can live as you wish.
手にできるかはあなた次第
Whether you get it depends on you,
隠したりなんかはしない
I won't hide anything.
誰よりも誇らしげに
More proudly than anyone else,
できる MIND
A mind that can do it.
ほらこの世界の中
Look, inside this world,
他にはない
There is nothing else.
確かなもの
The only certain thing,
自分以外は皆無
Aside from yourself, is non-existent.
Chi-chi-tack の Bell, by time じゃない
The ticking bell, it's not by time,
いつだって no time, all right
Always no time, all right.
Don't get it, go engine
全開で each time burn, burn, burn
Full throttle, each time burn, burn, burn.
欲しがってんのはそう
What you want is, yes,
気持ちいいの more
More of the good feeling.
あるがままの想い入れ
Putting in your feelings as they are,
Just 言いなりで get down
Just do as told and get down!
いらない 全てはいらない
I don't need it, I don't need anything.
磨き上げてる邪魔な PRIDE
That polished, hindering pride,
無意味な世界のルール
The meaningless rules of the world,
くらい無駄としか言いようがない
Can only be called a dark waste.
隠しているあなたの STYLE
Your style that you are hiding,
剥き出しにあるがまま DIVE
Dive in, bare and as you are.
そこに生まれるのは期待
What is born there is expectation,
外れなんかじゃない
It's not a disappointment.
頂きの SMILE
A smile from the peak.
ほらこの世界で今
Look, in this world now,
解き放って
Unleash it,
鋭くギラつかせた希望
The hope that glares sharply.
もっと本気出していいよ
You can get more serious.
Ah...
Ow!
Come chase me.
Web of danger,
spun around my lips so intricate.
On the way out,
my heart got torn to shreds, so complicated.
Better see ya,
I'm just a masochist,
sick of being pointed at, him.
You ain't gonna ever get this.
Pedal to the metal
shooting straight to the stars.
Got a craving like the danger on me.
Yes tonight, feel like, feel like that.
Up another level,
temptation you just can't deny.
Come get a taste,
but can't say I won't bite.
So put it on me, ay!
In my highest nirvana
One ticket
pushing for the high
My lever
I gotta run
But it's fun to see you try
So hit me up!
Off the map
I'mma take all my energy up
Speed enough
Ready, target locked
Hit the dash
I'm upgrading, and you wanna stop
So hit me up, ah
I never stop
In a new territory
On the edge of glory
Boy, just watch how I move
Give me that rush
Gonna regret in my mind
Boys on you this time
So hit me up, out of luck for your love
You got a crush?
Such a cliche, your bad boy charms
Fold and fall right back in your arms
Wasn't enough, you needed more
Now you begging to let you score
Shame you're thinking all is right
Don't be visiting tonight
Goodbye, goodbye
Gonna leave you dry
Always wanna play it cool
20/20 vision on me
Just the sight and feel of you
Like the, like the, like the...
Engine booming, that's my cue
Catch me if you can, you better
Keep up the chase, boy
Falling behind
Super style, I'm
Headed out
I'm gonna, ah
In my highest nirvana
One ticket
pushing for the high
My lever
I gotta run
But it's fun to see you try
So hit me up!
Off the map
I'mma take all my energy up
Speed enough
Ready, target locked
So hit me up!
Hit the dash
I'm upgrading, and you wanna stop
So hit me up, ah
I never stop
In a new territory
I'm on the edge of glory
Boy, just watch how I move
Give me that rush
Gonna regret in my mind
Boys on you this time
So hit me up, out of luck for your love
You got a crush?
Just barely wasn't enough
You shoulda
You put me on that you get
You coulda
Coming full circle
I've had enough
Top spot
Getting hot
Watch me run it up
Rev it up and make that vroom vroom vroom vroom
Hit me up
When I hit you with that zoom zoom zoom zoom
If you know what's good for you-u-u-u
With me
Now I'm back in charge
Right out of the dark
Yeah! I hope you enjoyed that!
Did you guys enjoy it?
We had a couple of songs...
with a couple of important people...
which I wanna call in to help with this next MC part.
Special guests!
Hey, hey, hey!
What's up? 皆さん！
What's up? Everyone!
Hey!
Ah, introduce yourselves please.
Please go ahead.
HoloLive English CHAD CASTの森カリオペです！
It's Mori Calliope from HoloLive English CHAD CAST!
What's up? ですです！
What's up? Desu desu!
Hey guys!
Hope you enjoyed our performances!
Yeah! And...
HiRyS, it's IRyS!
Also from CHAD CAST!
Yeah, let's go!
Yeah! Damn!
Here to rumble!
Yeah!
What's this movement?
Rumble! I said rumble!
I'm pretty sure she said IRyS.
Oh, my brain's not working.
It's a big day, guys.
'Cause you're dancing.
Yeah. It's a big day.
Guys!
Yeah?
Oh, yeah. I mean, yeah, obviously yeah.
Woo!
What do you think?
It's so cool!
You look like a K-pop star.
Aww, yeah!
I'm so glad you like it.
And look, the MC tail is back, you know.
I gotta put it to rest for a little bit.
You know, after all that dancing.
So special.
Don't touch it! Don't touch it!
But we performed some songs together.
First we had... Ifu...
ちょっと待って！
Wait a minute!
Ba-di-da-da!
Well, I guess it's on brand.
Yeah...
Yeah, we know.
Awesome. It's great.
It was a sexy song.
How do you feel about that song? Thank you so much.
How do I feel?
Yeah.
How do you feel about that song?
Feelings, thoughts, opinions?
I feel great about it!
She's embraced herself.
Which guys...
Which hit?
So hit me up!
Hit me up. Yeah.
I'm so happy...
I was able...
Well practiced.
Yeah we did. We practiced so hard.
It's always fun practicing together though.
Three of us... two of us at a time...
It's always fun.
Birthday!
Not birthday.
Birthday but not birthday.
Unbirthday.
She's being un-birthed.
But... what?
That sounds so wrong!
Saved for the Chad Cast.
I was saver of the Chad Cast.
But after dancing I am feeling a little bit, you know...
Hot?
Hot.
Shit's getting hot in here.
Is she gonna take off all her clothes?
Whoa!
Hey, your stream is...
Maybe no...
I'ma be right back.
Oh! What is she taking off?
Is she gonna take off her pants?
Why would she take off her pants, IRyS?
What is she thinking about?
Why is she taking it off?
Alright, you know what?
Okay, wait no...
Stop, you need to be stopped.
悪童ぞ？
You brat?
Oh! She coming in.
Whoa!
Behold!
Ohh!
I took off my jacket!
Oh my god, she looks so fancy.
Sexy!
Yeah, you can see all my... all my accessories now.
カッコいい！
Cool!
I have like a sweatband.
I love the spikes.
It's like a sweatband. Yeah.
いいですね。
Very nice.
いいその袖。
Those sleeves are nice.
But I have like a arm cuff now as well.
Eh, cool!
Now I can dance even more with no restriction!
She's even more dynamic.
More dynamic!
My god.
Not more dynamic.
Yes!
Yeah no pigtails to get in the way either, like...
Oh my god, she's poppin' off.
All the arms.
まあ、せっかくなのでね Since we're all here together...
Well, since we're here... Since we're all here together...
Uh-huh?
How would you guys feel about maybe doing one more song together?
Okay!
I don't have the energy but I'll do my best!
頑張れ、頑張れ、頑張れ、頑張れ！
Do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best!
Yay!
So with that being said, I hope you guys are ready as well.
We're gonna bring you one more Chad Cast... uh, performance!
Let's Go!
Yeah!
Ready, se-no!
Let's Go!
始まる始まる始まる！
It's starting, it's starting, it's starting!
宿題が全然終わらない
My homework isn't finishing at all!
全国のヤバめな諸君
To all the panicked folks nationwide!
時間がなければ眠らなきゃいいじゃない
If there's no time, just don't sleep, right?
ガンバレガンバレ私
Do your best, do your best, me!
パーリラのナイトフロア
The party-la night floor is...
暴れてるカルナバル
...a raging carnival!
アドレナリンドバドバ
Adrenaline is gushing out!
究極の PANIGHT
The ultimate PANIGHT!
PANIGHT! PANIGHT!
パラパパ PANIGHT!
Para-papa PANIGHT!
PANIGHT! PANIGHT!
終わるくナイ？
Isn't it ending?
We are!
NEGI-U!
Let's Go!
すごい ヤバイ パない
Amazing, dangerous, insane!
物足りない
Not enough!
ナイナイ尽くしで留め処ない
Endless 'nots' with no stopping point!
すごい ヤバイ パない
Amazing, dangerous, insane!
Saturday Night
とにかくもうやるしかない
Anyway, just gotta do it!
ドスコイ！
Dosukoi!
ヤバイ パない
Dangerous, insane!
物足りない
Not enough!
全力... もしたい！
I want to go all out!
たった一度の青春は
This one-time youth is...
毎日エンジョイ Party Night
Enjoy everyday, Party Night!
お集まりの旦那様？
To all the gathered masters?
え？そうじゃないサマー？
Eh? That's not it, summer?
ご唱和ください
Please join in the chant!
それゆけ Say!
Here we go, Say!
Wa-o!
G-G-G-G-J!
Pa! Pa! Pa! Pa!
パない！
Panai!
Everybody Sing Along!
ブチ上げ Sing Along
Get hyped, Sing Along!
陽キャでも陰キャでも
Whether you're an extrovert or introvert...
勉強だワッショイワッショイ
...it's study time, Wasshoi Wasshoi!
ダイヤはギンカ系？
Diamonds are milky way?
おしゃべり No No No!
Chattering No No No!
遊んじゃダメダメ
Don't play around, no no!
ごめんなさーい！
I'm sorrryyy!
朝が来て 眠れない
Morning has come and I can't sleep.
どうしよう
What should I do?
神様も
Even God...
両手あげて Fly High
...raises both hands, Fly High!
なんとかなるしかない
We just have to make it work somehow!
頑張れ出来るって
Do your best, you can do it!
ド派手にかましたるね
I'll show off super flashily, okay?
Party People Put Your Hands Up!
PANIGHT! PANIGHT!
パラパパ PANIGHT!
Para-papa PANIGHT!
PANIGHT! PANIGHT!
時間がナイ！
There's no time!
We are!
NEGI-U!
Let's Go!
Woo! Let's Go!
すごい ヤバイ パない
Amazing, dangerous, insane!
物足りない
Not enough!
大抵のバッター 片付けない
Can't clean up most batters!
すごい ヤバイ パない
Amazing, dangerous, insane!
Sunday Night
とにかくもうやるしかない
Anyway, just gotta do it!
ドスコイ！
Dosukoi!
ヤバイ パない
Dangerous, insane!
物足りない
Not enough!
宿題やっぱり終わらない
Homework still isn't finishing!
たった一度の青春は
This one-time youth is...
脳内 Happy Party Night
In-brain Happy Party Night!
IRyS scary!
怖いよ〜
I'm scared~
ねえねえ
Hey hey.
この問題全然分かんないんですけど
I don't understand this question at all...
We all have no idea.
めっちゃ可愛いいんじゃん！
Isn't it super cute!
でしょ？
Right?
キラキラ光るんですよ
It sparkles and shines.
みんな元気だなぁ
Everyone is so energetic.
火曜キャってこんな時もすごいなぁ
Tuesday-Characters are amazing even at times like this.
Yeah yeah.
Party Party.
お描きになったそんな音楽 現在使われておりません
That music you wrote is currently not in use.
もう一度書き直してください
Please rewrite it once more.
意味わかんねー
I don't get it!
どうせ誰も聴いてないさ
Nobody's listening anyway.
音楽なんて全部ファッション
Music is all just fashion.
音楽なんてセンス退場はない
There's no retiring from taste in music.
どうせ何も伝えたくないさ
I don't want to convey anything anyway.
なんとなく得とって売名
Just gaining some profit and fame somehow.
あんな気取っておいて最低じゃない？
Acting all pretentious like that, isn't it the worst?
どうしたってどう見たって
No matter what, no matter how you look,
喪失者でも大渋滞
it's a massive traffic jam even for the lost.
それでもあちこちそっちどっち
Even so, here, there, everywhere,
マインドセット演出されるの欲しがる
wanting a mindset produced for them.
パンチライン欲しいの
I want a punchline.
意味とかどっちだっていいよ
Meaning or whatever doesn't matter.
価値とかどうでもいいので
Value and such doesn't matter,
ノれるのください
just give me something to vibe to.
さあみんなで笑いましょう
Come on, let's all laugh together.
芸術より数の代償
The price of numbers over art.
ウイルスに酷い代償
A terrible price for the virus.
じゃあどうすんのそれでいいんだっけ
So what do we do? Is that okay?
頭空回り死んでいく
Spinning my wheels in my head, dying.
Found myself instead
ふざけるなバイバイバズメロディー
Don't screw with me, bye-bye buzz melody.
疑えよ大概嘘ばかり
Doubt it, it's mostly lies anyway.
馬鹿な幻想でも理想でもいい
Stupid illusions or ideals, it doesn't matter.
君の歌いたかったもんはどうしたんだい
What happened to the things you wanted to sing?
様でもAll Right嘘じゃない
Even just appearances, it's all right, it's not a lie.
お金や偽装で満たす前に
Before filling up on money and disguises,
負けんな覚醒せよ鼓動たちよ
don't lose! Awaken, you beating hearts!
君の伝えたかったもんはどうしたんだい
What happened to the things you wanted to convey?
意味わかんねー
I don't get it!
お描きになったそんな音楽 現在使われておりません
That music you wrote is currently not in use.
POPソングHITソング聴いてもう一度書き直してください
Listen to pop songs and hit songs, and rewrite it.
ああもうハイカラ作家ばっかしゃらくさいわ
Ah, geez, all these trendy writers are so annoying.
あぁこいつもこいつもそいつもあいつも
Ah, this guy, that guy, everyone!
意味わかんねー
I don't get it!
どうしたってどう見たって
No matter what, no matter how you look,
喪失者でも大渋滞
it's a massive traffic jam even for the lost.
それでもあちこちそっちどっち
Even so, here, there, everywhere,
マインドセット演出されるの欲しがる
wanting a mindset produced for them.
パンチライン欲しいの
I want a punchline.
意味とかどっちだっていいよ
Meaning or whatever doesn't matter.
価値とかどうでもいいので
Value and such doesn't matter,
ノれるのください
just give me something to vibe to.
さあみんなで払いましょう
Come on, let's all pay up.
芸術より数なんでしょ
It's numbers over art, right?
ウイルスに酷い代償
A terrible price for the virus.
じゃあどうすんのそれでいいんだっけ
So what do we do? Is that okay?
頭空回り死んでいく
Spinning my wheels in my head, dying.
Found myself instead
ふざけるなバイバイバズメロディー
Don't screw with me, bye-bye buzz melody.
疑えよ大概嘘ばかり
Doubt it, it's mostly lies anyway.
馬鹿な幻想でも理想でもいい
Stupid illusions or ideals, it doesn't matter.
君の歌いたかったもんはどうしたんだい
What happened to the things you wanted to sing?
このままじゃ到底終われない
We can't end it like this.
欲しいのはきっとお金じゃない
What we want surely isn't money.
変な覚醒せよ鼓動たちよ
Strange awakening, arise! You beating hearts!
君の歌いたかったもんを見つけたんだ
I found the thing you wanted to sing!
ふざけるな
Don't screw with me!
ふざけるなバイバイバズメロディー
Don't screw with me, bye-bye buzz melody.
疑えよ大概嘘ばかり
Doubt it, it's mostly lies anyway.
馬鹿な幻想でも理想でもいい
Stupid illusions or ideals, it doesn't matter.
君の歌いたかったもんはどうしたんだい
What happened to the things you wanted to sing?
歌までもAll Right嘘じゃない
Even the song is all right, it's not a lie.
お金や偽装で満たす前に
Before filling up on money and disguises,
負けんな覚醒せよ鼓動たちよ
don't lose! Awaken, you beating hearts!
僕の伝えたかったもんはどうしたんだい
What happened to the things I wanted to convey?
意味わかんねー
I don't get it!
意味わかんねーよ
I really don't get it!
Virtual blah blah blah
I'm a V
I'm a V da la V da la V da la...
Blah blah blah
高々生等の混沌
Chaos of mere existence,
触らば可愛いの混沌
chaos that's cute if you touch it.
届かな遥かなるホラ
Look, it's unreachable and far away.
落としてあげる
I'll make you fall for it.
ハイソメンヘラ
High-society menhera,
でも面がCUTEならメンキラー
but if the face is CUTE, she's a man-killer.
ちょっとハララ垂れてるイッてるメンタルは
Her mental state is a bit dripping and gone crazy.
最強SMILEで
With the strongest SMILE,
誤魔化してくPHANTOM
deceiving like a PHANTOM.
誤魔化したら正真正銘去る去る去る BYE BYE
If you deceive, it's genuinely leaving leaving leaving BYE BYE.
なんてな
Just kidding.
I am a V
I am a 泡 泡 よ
I am a bubble, bubble, yo!
I am a V da la diva 淫らわよよ
I am a V da la diva, I'm lewd, yo yo!
夢見てる少年
The boy who's dreaming,
夢見てる少女へ
to the girl who's dreaming,
VならVだわ甘甘甘甘の
if it's V, it's V, sweet sweet sweet sweet...
ちょん切るガリガリ妄想
Snipping off the skinny delusions.
Whatever said no
俺がセンター
I am the center.
誰よりも曲を千のパンジャー
More than anyone, a thousand songs of panther.
Whateverなんだまるで運だ
Whatever it is, it's just like luck.
自己愛性症状
Narcissistic symptoms.
Why me so lovely?
My name is blah blah
乱れたなら墓まで Love だ
If it's chaotic, it's Love until the grave
I'm a V だ ならばまた心の中 smooth like a butter
I'm a V, if so, inside my heart again, smooth like a butter
Touch me したいならほら endo
If you want to Touch me, look, it's the end
Catch me da high peace
Catch me, the high peace
見透かす枠が分からないわ
I don't understand the scope I see through
我心叫ぶ一つの life
My heart screams, one life
生きる姿や魂を今
The living figure and soul, now
二つにして愛をバラバラに
Split in two, tearing love apart
生まれた時の喜びは
The joy of when I was born
墓標にサヨナラでいいの？
Is it okay to say goodbye to the grave marker?
ダメね
No good, huh
Watch out! Watch out!
Watch out wa mekka mekka
Watch out is mecca mecca
Watch out! Watch out!
Watch out wa mekka mekka la
Watch out is mecca mecca la
カルマの鐘
The bell of Karma
あらら好感度ようかね
Oh my, is it for favorability?
絶対に正体ね
Definitely the true form, right?
あら？
Oh?
Watch out wa mekka mekka la
Watch out is mecca mecca la
カルマの鐘
The bell of Karma
あらら好感度ようかね
Oh my, is it for favorability?
遺憾の終わりだね
It's a regrettable end, isn't it
I am a V
I'm a V
I'm a awa awa yo
I'm a bubble bubble yo
I am a V da ma diva
Midara wa yaya yo
Obscenity is no no
夢見てる少年や
Dreaming boys and
夢見てる少女へ
to the dreaming girls
V nara V da wa
If it's V, then it's V
Ama ama ama ama no
Sweet sweet sweet sweet
教養さ
Culture/Education
子供の頃言われたもんだ
I was told when I was a child
あのヒーローショーの人形の背中には
On the back of that hero show doll
チャックがついてないじゃない
Wait, there's no zipper attached, right?
Watch out the human
推しの子の優雅
The elegance of the favorite child/Idol
存在は One One だ
Existence is One One
惚れても惚れても死ぬほどバラバラだ
Fall in love, fall in love, but it's scattered to death
Watch out blah blah
Blah blah blah blah!
Watch out blah blah blah
Are you ready for...?
惚れたら死ぬぞ
If you fall in love, you'll die
Watch out blah blah
Mmmm, I'm a V!
あー！疲れた！
Ah! I'm tired!
I'm so tired!
I hope you guys have been enjoying the show!
We had so many bangers after bangers after bangers!
A lot of dancing!
We had Play Dice,
we had Cyberpunk Dead Boy,
we had V...
My arms are dead! Everything dead.
But that's not the end of the show yet!
We gotta keep going on and on and on and on and on!
And here I bring you a very very very important and... exciting announcement!
Um, I am about to perform a song that no one has heard before.
No one! Except for me.
Because it's my new song!
Um, I've been hyping this up for a while now,
because I'm really really excited.
And this will be the first time that I'm sharing... sharing it with all of you.
So I hope you enjoy!
More information after I perform it 'cause you gotta see it first, you know?
Wish me luck!
Um, I'm nervous but... we got this.
今回は… なんと新曲です！
This time... it's a new song!
めちゃくちゃ緊張なんだけど
I'm super nervous but
頑張ってパフォーマンスしたいと思います
I want to do my best performing it
どうぞ！
Here you go!
준비~!
Ready~!
That's good game what a shame
Play is the your complain
Why me no not again
Shut up top spot
Ain't got time so dry those eyes
Look around what satisfied the broken and bruised
I got something to prove now
Abracadabra let's go
Watch em like dice as they fall
끝까지 가보자고
Let's go until the end
난 마음대로 해
I do as I please
Hey!
Double one double one, we're rollin' the lottery too
Alright I... we hit that high
Snake Eyes Snake Eyes
Come on now don't be shy
즐겁게 놀아볼래
I wanna play happily
Uh-huh
Loser outta your night all night
Don't turn it off
Can't stop won't stop preaching
Who said the sky's the limit
Show them that we mean business
We are the young ambitious
Snake eyes they never lie
Fly high with pride and leave your fears behind
우리들의 광란の party
Our frenzy party
보여줄게 환상의 safari
I'll show you a fantasy safari
Bani bani nobody can stop me
Get it get it
I'm a closer
Go go
The bally...
Acting all naughty
Side double...
머저리...
Fool...
Shake it up
The dice will come back down, ready the fight,
ready the screaming.
Abracadabra let's go,
watch me ripping it all.
그 끝이 어디인지 (Geu kkeuti eodineunji)...
Where the end is...
Reason, a demon, believing the freedom,
just waiting and see.
We hit that high, Snake Eyes.
Come on now don't be shy, Snake Eyes.
Dumb-foundead, dollar, holler.
Move out the way all night.
Let the beat drop! Go!
We go hard! Go! Go! Go!
We go hard! I want it all.
運命の賭けだ (Unmei no kake da) Checkmate.
It's a gamble of fate, Checkmate.
全部賭けろ (Zenbu kakero) I want it all.
Bet everything, I want it all.
Take the crown.
그 끝이 달려가 (Geu kkeuti dallyeoga) Rule the game.
Run towards the end, Rule the game.
We'll hit that high, Snake Eyes.
勝つか負けるか (Katsu ka makeru ka) Snake Eyes.
Win or lose, Snake Eyes.
もう躊躇はない (Mou chuucho wa nai) Don't stop.
No more hesitation, Don't stop.
Don't be afraid of losing,
it's just a new beginning.
Look at the cards we're dealing,
sometimes it takes a villain.
Sing! Now is the time to fly.
Fly high with pride and leave our fears behind!
Ha ha ha! It's finally out!
I hope you all enjoyed my new song, Snake Eyes!
Snake Eyes, Snake Eyes, Snake Eyes...
This has been such a long process...
I can't even talk! I'm exhausted but also,
I'm so happy.
It's finally out! My newest song Snake Eyes...
was what I just performed.
Not only is it the first time that I've written
a lot of the lyrics from scratch,
but also it's the first time choreographing...
a multi-member song with the two back dancers.
I'm so happy! I did it!
I hope you guys enjoyed it.
Now, very important, pay attention!
The MV of this new song is also going to be
premiering very soon,
after the live is over.
And it is going to be my first ever
3D Music Video!
Oh, so excited!
やっとね新曲がちょっとね、公開するので、
Finally, the new song will be released,
めちゃくちゃ嬉しいです。
so I'm incredibly happy.
この後、ライブの後ね、初の3D MVもプレミアするので、
After this live, my first 3D MV will premiere,
見てて下さい！お願いします！
so please watch it! Please!
英語の歌詞はほぼ自分で書いたので、
あと韓国語もね、頑張ってたんで。
I wrote most of the English lyrics myself,
and I worked hard on the Korean too.
聞いてください！
Please listen to it!
Now it's time. It's the thing
you've all been waiting for.
A Merch Showcase!
グッズ紹介に入りたいと思います！
I'd like to start the goods introduction!
This is the lineup for this time!
Baelz Hakos 2026 Birthday Set.
フルセットはこんな感じです。
The full set looks like this.
Let's look at them one by one.
First up, 最初は何でしょう？
First up, what is the first one?
We have the [ReCOLOR] Rubber Mat!
Look at that beauty.
This illustration is of course by my beloved Mama,
Mika Pikazo-sensei.
今年も描いてくださってありがとうございます。
Thank you for drawing it this year as well.
My very first birthday merch also had a rubber mat,
and since I have a new outfit...
Look at it. It's so pretty. Thank you so much.
あのママ... 今年もね、ミカママに...
Umm, Mama... this year too, Mika-mama...
...あのイラスト描いてくださったので、ありがとうございます。
...drew the illustration for me, so thank you very much.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
ぜひぜひ買ってください。
Please, please buy it.
Eeto... what's the next item?
Umm... what's the next item?
Second is...
Tada! The ReCOLOR Plushie Keychain...
...designed after my new outfit!
I've always wanted like a... a mini, you know, um plushie that... that I came out with.
Um... you know, I have some but... I think... it was just... it was just really fitting cuz I have a new outfit.
And I wanted a plushie... in the new outfit.
I can take her around places... you know... and... you know... you can photograph her...
...chuck her... I don't know. Take... pat her... I don't know. Whatever you want to do.
But... it's a plushie keychain so it comes with a ball chain so you can attach it to your bag!
Isn't she so cute?
Look at those squishy cheeks.
めっちゃ可愛いでしょ？
Super cute, right?
キー... あの... ぬいぐるみキーホルダーなんで、なんかカバンに...
Key... um... it's a plushie keychain so, like on a bag...
...付けたりとかね、できるので。
...you can attach it and stuff so.
めちゃくちゃ可愛い感じになりました。
It turned out super cute.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
えーっと次。 What is the next one?
Umm, next. What is the next one?
これです！
This is it!
The Li'l Plushie Shed Pouch.
It is a pouch.
It is... a... a pouch for... the plushie.
If you... get both it's like a set... you know... because...
...you know you want to take your li'l Bae out into the world but what if... what if she gets dirty?
You know... or like... you know... you don't want her... to get to... you know if she gets snagged on a corner... if she rips.
You gotta protect... your li'l Bae. So... you have a li'l plushie shed.
To house your li'l Bae.
Um... but it fits perfectly and... you know... you can use it.
It... the design is also really cool as well.
Um... Next!
Last but not least...
...is... something very special. It is a voice pack.
But... it is my first... ever... ASMR voice pack.
Um... I... I get really embarrassed doing ASMR stuff...
...but I just thought... you know... since it's a special occasion...
...maybe it'd be nice... to have... my very first ASMR voice pack...
...it... it features... a... an intimate scene...
...with you guys... uh after the live show.
So if you want to... you know check it out... please do.
え... 僕初... 初... 初のASMRボイス... シナリオボイスなんで...
Umm... My first... first... first ASMR voice... scenario voice so...
...もし... 気に... 気になってる... 方は是非... 聞いてください。
...if... you're cu... curious... please... listen to it.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
It's called 'Forever Your Bae'.
恥ずかしい。
Embarrassing.
Anyway.
Here are the full set bonuses!
Da-da-da-da-dan! The Postcard!
You get a... limited edition which... uh... the limited edition, sorry...
...features a hand-signed autograph and also a hand-written message from yours truly.
Just a... extra way to say thank you very much.
Um... and the standard version comes with the foil-stamped duplicate... uh autograph and... message.
Arms about to... about to die but it's alright.
Uh... Thank you so much.
えーっと... 特... 特... 特... 特... ヤバい読め！
Um... spe... spe... spe... feature... Oh no, I can't read it!
え？... 漢字... 漢字が何だっけ？
Eh? ... The kanji... what was the kanji?
あの特... 特典はこちらです！
Um bon... the bonus is this!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
ポストカード...
Postcard...
えーっと... あの... ひ... 引き... ひ... 直筆... サイ... とメッセージがあります。
Um... uh... h... hand... h... handwritten... sign... and message are included.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
Oh my god my brain is just... it's gone. I'm so tired.
But... anyway... um... I think that's it.
Oh wait no! There's also a bonus voice! Wait I forgot.
Um... so with the full set... uh there is a bonus... voice... pack...
...that is also ASMR that's on top of the already ASMR voice pack.
Just a... little extra thing to say thank you.
Um... That's it. I'm... embarrassed. Anyway. Yes.
それだけです！
That's all!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
はい！
Yes!
Um... Yes.
Before... we continue... I guess... um... there is a little bit after...
So... I'm gonna go put my... jacket on... real quick.
If that's okay. I'll be right back.
ちょっと着替えてきます。
I'll go change a bit.
Ta-da! 戻ってきました。はい。ただいまです。
Ta-da! I'm back. Yes. I'm home.
Eeto... just put on my jacket.
Umm... just put on my jacket.
I'm... so... happy... that... you know... I got to do another birthday live this year...
Even though it's not really my birthday.
Um... I'm so happy... that I got... to show... my new outfit.
I'm just happy... that I got... a new outfit.
It's so easy to dance in. I love the way it looks.
And... today I got to dance with so many... uh of my friends.
It was so much fun.
Uh... I got to challenge myself.
It's always... an amazing... amazing experience... being able to do a birthday live.
いや今日ね... あの... いっぱい... のメンバーと一緒に踊ってめちゃくちゃ嬉しくて...
Yeah today... um... dancing with so many... members made me super happy...
もう新衣装もめちゃくちゃ嬉しくて... もうとにかく嬉しいです。
And the new outfit makes me super happy... and anyway I'm happy.
あの... みんなもね...
Um... everyone too...
There's a lot of planning that goes into these.
Um... a lot of all the staff and everyone.
Everyone's... 力...
Everyone's... power...
あー、が必要。もう何だこれ。
Uh, is necessary. What is this?
もう英語か日本語かもう分かんないっすね。すいません。
I don't know if it's English or Japanese anymore. Sorry.
Yes. I'm just mixing up my languages but...
Please do check out the new song MV that's coming out shortly.
I'm really, really proud of it.
Um, but that's kind of it.
That's all I have for today.
BUT!
There is a final encore song that I wanted to sing,
that I think really sums up today's live.
So, if you would like to stay till...
Ah, please stay to the end.
Please listen.
Please don't go anywhere.
ちょっとこの後、最後の一曲あります。
After this, there is one final song.
今日のテーマにぴったりの曲だと思いますので、
I think it's a song that fits today's theme perfectly, so,
最後まで聴いてください。
please listen until the end.
はい！
Yes!
あとMV... 新曲のMVも見てくださいね。はい。
Also the MV... please watch the new song's MV too. Yes.
じゃ、最後の曲。ラスト曲、どうぞ。
Well then, the last song. Last song, here you go.
魂の色は何色ですか
What color is the soul?
Thank you for coming to my live today!
I hope I brought some color to your day!
最後まで盛り上がっていこうぜ！
Let's get hyped until the very end!
もういっそ折れたままで
Might as well stay broken
捨てるほど逃げ出すほど
Enough to throw away, enough to run away
強くないよ
I'm not that strong
ほら もう一度鼓動高鳴る
Look, my heartbeat rises once more
何が正しいかなんて
I don't know what is 'correct'
分からないけど
But even so
形のないものばかりが
Only shapeless things
大切になっていく
Are becoming precious
飾らない言葉だけが
Only unadorned words
強く結ばれてる
Are strongly tied together
また躓いて転がって
Stumbling and rolling again
それでも砕けない
But still unbreakable
魂の色は何色ですか
What color is the soul?
ただ傷ついて強がって
Just getting hurt and acting tough
それでも見つけたいよ
But I still want to find it
魂のカタチ
The shape of the soul
確かめてるよ
I'm verifying it
不可知の底で一人
Alone at the bottom of the unknown
扉と鍵を探す
Searching for the door and key
お伽噺はほら
Fairy tales are, look...
泡のように全部消えて
Disappearing like bubbles
葛藤 残像だけ
Only conflict and afterimages
次のページへ
To the next page
伸びてく枝葉が別れて
The extending branches and leaves separate
それぞれの道を行く
Going their separate ways
寂しい思い出だけが
Only lonely memories
強く根を張ってる
Are rooting deeply
まだ貫いて失って
Still piercing through and losing
それでも挫けない
But still not discouraged
心は何処に 器は何処に
Where is the heart? Where is the vessel?
ただ残されて抜け落ちて
Just left behind and falling out
それでも伝えたいよ
But I still want to convey it
魂の日々は 魂の意志は
The days of the soul, the will of the soul
ずっと... Woah woah...
Forever... Woah woah...
魂の色は何色ですか
What color is the soul?
何色ですか...
What color is it...
赤い色ですか
Is it red?
青い色ですか
Is it blue?
魂の色は...
The color of the soul is...
透明な過去に 不透明な明日に
In the transparent past, in the opaque tomorrow
生きるあなたは何色ですか
What color are you, who lives?
また躓いて転がって
Stumbling and rolling again
それでも砕けない
But still unbreakable
魂の色は何色ですか
What color is the soul?
ただ傷ついて強がって...
Just getting hurt and acting tough...
見つけたよ
I found it.
魂の形
The shape of the soul.
確かめてるよ
I'm confirming it.
ずっと...
Always...
ウォー...
Woah...
ずっと...
Always...
ウォー...
Woah...